(Sheldon:)Is that what that was? I just assumed...
...that the second-grade curriculum
had rendered you quizzical.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Penny(knocking and entering, holding up a pair of superman undershorts.):)Hey, Leonard, you left your underwear
in the drier downstairs.
Pfft.
(Leonard:)Those are not mine.
Really? They have
your little name label in them.
Oh, yeah, no, I use those...
(Leonard:)...just to polish up
my spearfishing equipment.
I spearfish.
(Leonard:)When I'm not crossbow hunting,
(Leonard:)Penny, this is Sheldon's twin sister.
Missy, this is our neighbor Penny.
(Leonard:)- Hi.
- Wow, you don't look that much alike.
Can I get a hallelujah?
(Sheldon:)Fraternal twins
come from two separate eggs.
(Sheldon:)They are no more alike
than any other siblings.
(Howard:)Hallelujah.